NYSUT Publications 6174 PUBS
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation & Archives
NYSUT Publications
1965-1995
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation & Archives
New York State United Teachers (NYSUT)
6174 PUBS
20.28 cubic feet
20.1 linear ft.
Publications.
7164224
General
Contact Information:
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation and Archives Martin P. Catherwood Library 227 Ives Hall Cornell University Ithaca, NY 14853 (607) 255-3183> kheel_center@cornell.edu http://www.ilr.cornell.edu/library/kheel-center
Compiled by:
R. Miles, September 26, 2012
EAD encoding:
Randall Miles, February 24, 2016
Biographical / Historical
New York State United Teachers (NYSUT) was created in 1972 by the merger of the New York State Teachers Association (NYSTA) and the United Teachers of New York (UTNY). NYSTA had been affiliated with the National Education Association (NEA), and UTNY with the American Federation of Teachers (AFT). UTNY was the statewide organization whose United Federation of Teachers (UFT), led by Albert Shanker, was the predominant teachers' union in New York City. In joining with United Teachers and affiliating with the AFT, NYSUT also became a member union of the AFL-CIO.
In 1976, NYSUT voted to disaffiliate with the NEA. Some locals left NYSUT and created the NYEA (New York Educators Association), which became the state affiliate for the NEA. In the early 1980s, NYEA changed its name to NEA-NY.
NYEA/NEA- NY viewed association with the AFL-CIO's industrial unions as undermining the professional image and independence of teachers. The two organizations also differed strongly on aspects of the governance structure, particularly with respect to ethnic minority representation, with NYSUT opposed to mandatory minimums. The rivalry between NYSUT and NYEA/NEA-NY in organizing new locals expended a great deal of resources for both labor organizations.
While competition with NYEA/NEA-NY was a constant focus of NYSUT's organizing efforts for teachers, NYSUT was also organizing college faculty members, nurses, and other non-teaching personnel. Once members were organized, NYSUT continued to advocate for teachers' and other workers' rights through contract support and legal services at the local level and political involvement at the state and federal levels, supporting candidates and legislation that protected funding, due process, and working conditions.
NEA-N Y merged with NYSUT in 2006, by which time NYSUT had grown to more than half a million members, becoming the largest union in New York State.
Scope and Contents
Mostly issues of New York Teacher, the official newspaper of NYSUT, 1971-1995 (some earlier)
Conditions Governing Access
Access to the collections in the Kheel Center is restricted. Please contact a reference archivist for access to these materials.
Related Materials
Related Collections: 6174/017 MB: NYSUT General Officers Memorabilia 6174: NYSUT Records 6174 AV: NYSUT Audio-Visual Materials 6174 MB: NYSUT Memorabilia 6174 OH: NYSUT Oral History Interviews 6174 P: NYSUT Photographs 6174/001: NYSUT President's Office Files 6174/001 P: NYSUT President's Office Photographs 6174/002: NYSUT Vice President's Office files 6174/003: NYSUT Division of Research and Educational Services. Files 6174/004: NYSUT Field Services Department Files 6174/004 AV: NYSUT Field Services Department Audio-Visual Material 6174/005: NYSUT Legislative Department Files 6174/006: NYSUT Public Relations Department Files 6174/007: NYSUT New York Special Task Force on Equity and Excellence in Education Files 6174/008: NYSUT Federation of Nurses and Health Professionals Files 6174/009: NYSUT Teacher Education Conference Board Files 6174/010: NYSUT Convention files 6174/011: NYSUT Mid-Hudson Regional Office Files 6174/012: NYSUT "Teachers United: The Rise of NYSUT" Research Notes 6174/013 AV: NYSUT Representative Assembly (RA) Audio-Visual materials 6174/014: NYSUT Alan Lubin Files 6174/015: NYSUT Boards of Directors Meetings 6174/016: NYSUT Vice-President's Office Maria Neira. Files 6174/017: NYSUT General Officers Records 6174/017 AV: NYSUT General Officers Audio-Visual Materials 6174/017 P: NYSUT General Officers Photographs 6174/018: NYSUT Division of Research and Educational Services, Maria Neira Files 6174/019: NYSUT Biography File
Teachers' union -- New York (State); New York State United Teachers; New York State United Teachers --Publications
7164224
- New York Teacher (Box 1)
  - Box: 1, Folder: 1 (Box 1, Folder 1)
    - Item 1: New York Teacher, 1999; Publication (Box 1, Folder 1)
      Scope and Contents
      Author: NYSUT (New York State United Teachers)
      Notes: v.40:no.10 (1999:Feb. 10)
      Format: Publication
      Language: English.
  - Box: 1, Folder: 2, Publication (Box 1, Folder 2)
    - Item 1: New York Teacher, 2000; Publication (Box 1, Folder 2)
      Notes: v.41:no.16 (2000:May 3)
    - Item 2: New York Teacher, 2000; Publication (Box 1, Folder 2)
      Notes: v.41:no.18 (2000:May 31)
    - Item 3: New York Teacher, 2000; Publication (Box 1, Folder 2)
      Notes: v.42:no.1 (2000:Sept. 13)
    - Item 4: New York Teacher, 2000; Publication (Box 1, Folder 2)
      Notes: v.42:no.2 (2000:Sept. 27)
    - Item 5: New York Teacher, 2000; Publication (Box 1, Folder 2)
      Notes: v.42:no.3 (2000:Oct. 11)
    - Item 6: New York Teacher, 2000; Publication (Box 1, Folder 2)
      Notes: v.42:no.3 (2000:Oct. 11). Copy 2.
    - Item 7: New York Teacher, 2000; Publication (Box 1, Folder 2)
      Notes: v.42:no.4 (2000:Oct. 25)
    - Item 8: New York Teacher, 2000; Publication (Box 1, Folder 2)
      Notes: v.42:no.4 (2000:Oct. 25). Copy 2.
    - Item 9: New York Teacher, 2000; Publication (Box 1, Folder 2)
      Notes: v.42:no.5 (2000:Nov. 8)
    - Item 10: New York Teacher, 2000; Publication (Box 1, Folder 2)
      Notes: NYSUT-Cornell Leadership Institute. August 10, 2000.
    - Item 11: New York Teacher, 2000; Publication (Box 1, Folder 2)
      Notes: v.42:no.6 (2000:Nov. 22)
    - Item 12: New York Teacher, 2000; Publication (Box 1, Folder 2)
      Notes: v.42:no.6 (2000:Nov. 22). Copy 2.
    - Item 13: New York Teacher, 2000; Publication (Box 1, Folder 2)
      Notes: v.41:no.17 (2000:May 17)
    - Item 14: New York Teacher, 2000; Publication (Box 1, Folder 2)
      Notes: v.41:no.17 (2000:May 17). Copy 2.
    - Item 15: New York Teacher, 2000; Publication (Box 1, Folder 2)
      Notes: v.41:no.9 (2000:Jan. 26)
    - Item 16: New York Teacher, 2000; Publication (Box 1, Folder 2)
      Notes: v.41:no.10 (2000:Feb. 9)
    - Item 17: New York Teacher, 2000; Publication (Box 1, Folder 2)
      Notes: v.41:no.10 (2000:Feb. 9). Copy 2.
    - Item 18: New York Teacher, 2000; Publication (Box 1, Folder 2)
      Notes: v.41:no.11 (2000:Feb. 23)
    - Item 19: New York Teacher, 2000; Publication (Box 1, Folder 2)
      Notes: v.41:no.12 (2000:Mar. 6)
    - Item 20: New York Teacher, 2000; Publication (Box 1, Folder 2)
      Notes: v.41:no.12 (2000:Mar. 6). Copy 2.
    - Item 21: New York Teacher, 2000; Publication (Box 1, Folder 2)
      Notes: v.41:no.13 (2000:Mar. 22)
    - Item 22: New York Teacher, 2000; Publication (Box 1, Folder 2)
      Notes: v.41:no.14 (2000:Apr. 5)
    - Item 23: New York Teacher, 2000; Publication (Box 1, Folder 2)
      Notes: v.41:no.15 (2000:Apr. 19)
    - Item 24: New York Teacher, 2000; Publication (Box 1, Folder 2)
      Notes: v.41:no.15 (2000:Apr. 19). Copy 2.
    - Item 25: New York Teacher, 2000; Publication (Box 1, Folder 2)
      Notes: v.42:no.7 (2000:Dec. 6)
  - Box: 1, Folder: 3, Publication (Box 1, Folder 3)
    - Item 1: New York Teacher, 2001; Publication (Box 1, Folder 3)
      Notes: v.42:no.8 (2001:Jan. 17)
    - Item 2: New York Teacher, 2001; Publication (Box 1, Folder 3)
      Notes: v.42:no.8 (2001:Jan. 17). Copy 2.
    - Item 3: New York Teacher, 2001; Publication (Box 1, Folder 3)
      Notes: v.42:no.9 (2001:Jan. 31)
    - Item 4: New York Teacher, 2001; Publication (Box 1, Folder 3)
      Notes: v.42:no.10 (2001:Feb. 14)
    - Item 5: New York Teacher, 2001; Publication (Box 1, Folder 3)
      Notes: v.42:no.11 (2001:Feb. 28)
    - Item 6: New York Teacher, 2001; Publication (Box 1, Folder 3)
      Notes: v.42:no.12 (2001:Mar. 14)
    - Item 7: New York Teacher, 2001; Publication (Box 1, Folder 3)
      Notes: v.43:no.4 (2001:Oct. 24)
    - Item 8: New York Teacher, 2001; Publication (Box 1, Folder 3)
      Notes: v.43:no.5 (2001:Nov. 7)
    - Item 9: New York Teacher, 2001; Publication (Box 1, Folder 3)
      Notes: v.43:no.5 (2001:Nov. 7). Copy 2.
    - Item 10: New York Teacher, 2001; Publication (Box 1, Folder 3)
      Notes: v.43:no.6 (2001:Nov. 21)
    - Item 11: New York Teacher, 2001; Publication (Box 1, Folder 3)
      Notes: v.43:no.7 (2001:Dec. 5)
    - Item 12: New York Teacher, 2001; Publication (Box 1, Folder 3)
      Notes: v.42:no.13 (2001:Mar. 28)
    - Item 13: New York Teacher, 2001; Publication (Box 1, Folder 3)
      Notes: v.42:no.14 (2001:Apr. 11)
    - Item 14: New York Teacher, 2001; Publication (Box 1, Folder 3)
      Notes: v.42:no.15 (2001:Apr. 25)
    - Item 15: New York Teacher, 2001; Publication (Box 1, Folder 3)
      Notes: v.42:no.16 (2001:May 9)
    - Item 16: New York Teacher, 2001; Publication (Box 1, Folder 3)
      Notes: v.42:no.16 (2001:May 9). Copy 2.
    - Item 17: New York Teacher, 2001; Publication (Box 1, Folder 3)
      Notes: v.42:no.17 (2001:May 23)
    - Item 18: New York Teacher, 2001; Publication (Box 1, Folder 3)
      Notes: v.42:no.18 (2001:June 6)
    - Item 19: New York Teacher, 2001; Publication (Box 1, Folder 3)
      Notes: v.42:no.18 (2001:June 6). Copy 2.
    - Item 20: New York Teacher, 2001; Publication (Box 1, Folder 3)
      Notes: v.42:no.19 (2001:June 20)
    - Item 21: New York Teacher, 2001; Publication (Box 1, Folder 3)
      Notes: v.42:no.19 (2001:June 20). Copy 2.
    - Item 22: New York Teacher, 2001; Publication (Box 1, Folder 3)
      Notes: v.43:no.1 (2001:Sept. 12)
    - Item 23: New York Teacher, 2001; Publication (Box 1, Folder 3)
      Notes: v.43:no.1 (2001:Sept. 12). Copy 2.
    - Item 24: New York Teacher, 2001; Publication (Box 1, Folder 3)
      Notes: v.43:no.2 (2001:Sept. 26)
    - Item 25: New York Teacher, 2001; Publication (Box 1, Folder 3)
      Notes: v.43:no.3 (2001:Oct. 10)
  - Box: 1, Folder: 4, Publication (Box 1, Folder 4)
    - Item 1: New York Teacher, 2002; Publication (Box 1, Folder 4)
      Notes: v.43:no.19 (2002:June 19)
    - Item 2: New York Teacher, 2002; Publication (Box 1, Folder 4)
      Notes: v.44:no.1 (2002:Sept. 11)
    - Item 3: New York Teacher, 2002; Publication (Box 1, Folder 4)
      Notes: v.43:no.8 (2002:Jan. 16)
    - Item 4: New York Teacher, 2002; Publication (Box 1, Folder 4)
      Notes: v.43:no.9 (2002:Jan. 30)
    - Item 5: New York Teacher, 2002; Publication (Box 1, Folder 4)
      Notes: v.43:no.9 (2002:Jan. 30). Copy 2.
    - Item 6: New York Teacher, 2002; Publication (Box 1, Folder 4)
      Notes: v.43:no.10 (2002:Feb. 13)
    - Item 7: New York Teacher, 2002; Publication (Box 1, Folder 4)
      Notes: v.43:no.10 (2002:Feb. 13). Copy 2.
    - Item 8: New York Teacher, 2002; Publication (Box 1, Folder 4)
      Notes: v.43:no.11 (2002:Feb. 27)
    - Item 9: New York Teacher, 2002; Publication (Box 1, Folder 4)
      Notes: v.43:no.11 (2002:Feb. 27). Copy 2.
    - Item 10: New York Teacher, 2002; Publication (Box 1, Folder 4)
      Notes: v.43:no.12 (2002:Mar. 13)
    - Item 11: New York Teacher, 2002; Publication (Box 1, Folder 4)
      Notes: v.43:no.12 (2002:Mar. 13). Copy 2.
    - Item 12: New York Teacher, 2002; Publication (Box 1, Folder 4)
      Notes: v.43:no.13 (2002:Mar. 27)
    - Item 13: New York Teacher, 2002; Publication (Box 1, Folder 4)
      Notes: v.43:no.13 (2002:Mar. 27). Copy 2.
    - Item 14: New York Teacher, 2002; Publication (Box 1, Folder 4)
      Notes: v.43:no.14 (2002:Apr. 10)
    - Item 15: New York Teacher, 2002; Publication (Box 1, Folder 4)
      Notes: v.43:no.15 (2002:Apr. 24)
    - Item 16: New York Teacher, 2002; Publication (Box 1, Folder 4)
      Notes: v.43:no.16 (2002:May 8)
    - Item 17: New York Teacher, 2002; Publication (Box 1, Folder 4)
      Notes: v.43:no.17 (2002:May 22)
    - Item 18: New York Teacher, 2002; Publication (Box 1, Folder 4)
      Notes: v.43:no.18 (2002:June 5)
  - Box: 1, Folder: 5, Publication (Box 1, Folder 5)
    - Item 1: New York Teacher, 2003; Publication (Box 1, Folder 5)
      Notes: v.44:no.9 (2003:Jan. 29)
    - Item 2: New York Teacher, 2003; Publication (Box 1, Folder 5)
      Notes: v.44:no.11 (2003:Feb. 26)
    - Item 3: New York Teacher, 2003; Publication (Box 1, Folder 5)
      Notes: v.44:no.13 (2003:Maar. 26)
    - Item 4: New York Teacher, 2003; Publication (Box 1, Folder 5)
      Notes: v.44:no.15 (2003:Apr. 23)
    - Item 5: New York Teacher, 2003; Publication (Box 1, Folder 5)
      Notes: v.44:no.19 (2003:June 18)
    - Item 6: New York Teacher, 2003; Publication (Box 1, Folder 5)
      Notes: v.44:no.19 (2003:June 18). Copy 2.
    - Item 7: New York Teacher, 2003; Publication (Box 1, Folder 5)
      Notes: v.45:no.2 (2003:Sept. 24)
    - Item 8: New York Teacher, 2003; Publication (Box 1, Folder 5)
      Notes: v.45:no.3 (2003:Oct. 8)
    - Item 9: New York Teacher, 2003; Publication (Box 1, Folder 5)
      Notes: v.45:no.7 (2003:Dec. 3)
  - Box: 1, Folder: 6, Publication (Box 1, Folder 6)
    - Item 1: New York Teacher, 2004; Publication (Box 1, Folder 6)
      Notes: v.45:no.8 (2004:Jan. 14)
    - Item 2: New York Teacher, 2004; Publication (Box 1, Folder 6)
      Notes: v.45:no.9 (2004:Jan. 28)
    - Item 3: New York Teacher, 2004; Publication (Box 1, Folder 6)
      Notes: v.45:no.12 (2004:Mar. 10)
    - Item 4: New York Teacher, 2004; Publication (Box 1, Folder 6)
      Notes: v.45:no.18 (2004:June 2)
    - Item 5: New York Teacher, 2004; Publication (Box 1, Folder 6)
      Notes: v.46:no.1 (2004:Aug. 2)
    - Item 6: New York Teacher, 2004; Publication (Box 1, Folder 6)
      Notes: v.46:no.2 (2004:Sept. 9)
  - Box: 1, Folder: 7, Publication (Box 1, Folder 7)
    - Item 1: New York Teacher, 2005; Publication (Box 1, Folder 7)
      Notes: v.46:no.9 (2005:Jan. 20)
    - Item 2: New York Teacher, 2005; Publication (Box 1, Folder 7)
      Notes: v.46:no.10 (2005:Feb. 3)
    - Item 3: New York Teacher, 2005; Publication (Box 1, Folder 7)
      Notes: v.46:no.12 (2005:Mar. 3)
    - Item 4: New York Teacher, 2005; Publication (Box 1, Folder 7)
      Notes: v.46:no.13 (2005:Mar. 17)
    - Item 5: New York Teacher, 2005; Publication (Box 1, Folder 7)
      Notes: v.46:no.16 (2005:Apr. 28)
    - Item 6: New York Teacher, 2005; Publication (Box 1, Folder 7)
      Notes: v.46:no.17 (2005:May 12)
    - Item 7: New York Teacher, 2005; Publication (Box 1, Folder 7)
      Notes: v.47:no.1 (2005:Sept. 8)
    - Item 8: New York Teacher, 2005; Publication (Box 1, Folder 7)
      Notes: v.47:no.4 (2005:Oct. 20)
    - Item 9: New York Teacher, 2005; Publication (Box 1, Folder 7)
      Notes: v.47:no.5 (2005:Nov. 3)
    - Item 10: New York Teacher, 2005; Publication (Box 1, Folder 7)
      Notes: v.47:no.7 (2005:Dec. 8)
  - Box: 1, Folder: 8, Publication (Box 1, Folder 8)
    - Item 1: New York Teacher, 2006; Publication (Box 1, Folder 8)
      Notes: v.47:no.9 (2006:Feb. 2)
    - Item 2: New York Teacher, 2006; Publication (Box 1, Folder 8)
      Notes: v.47:no.10 (2006:Feb. 16)
    - Item 3: New York Teacher, 2006; Publication (Box 1, Folder 8)
      Notes: v.47:no.11 (2006:Mar. 2)
    - Item 4: New York Teacher, 2006; Publication (Box 1, Folder 8)
      Notes: v.47:no.12 (2006:Mar. 16)
    - Item 5: New York Teacher, 2006; Publication (Box 1, Folder 8)
      Notes: v.47:no.15 (2006:Apr. 27)
    - Item 6: New York Teacher, 2006; Publication (Box 1, Folder 8)
      Notes: v.47:no.14 (2006:May 11)
    - Item 7: New York Teacher, 2006; Publication (Box 1, Folder 8)
      Notes: v.47:no.17 (2006:May 26)
    - Item 8: New York Teacher, 2006; Publication (Box 1, Folder 8)
      Notes: v.48:no.1 (2006:Sept. 7)
    - Item 9: New York Teacher, 2006; Publication (Box 1, Folder 8)
      Notes: v.48:no.2 (2006:Sept. 21)
    - Item 10: New York Teacher, 2006; Publication (Box 1, Folder 8)
      Notes: v.48:no.6 (2006:Nov. 16)
    - Item 11: New York Teacher, 2006; Publication (Box 1, Folder 8)
      Notes: v.48:no.7 (2006:Dec. 7)
  - Box: 1, Folder: 9, Publication (Box 1, Folder 9)
    - Item 1: New York Teacher, 2007; Publication (Box 1, Folder 9)
      Notes: v.48:no.8 (2007:Jan. 18)
    - Item 2: New York Teacher, 2007; Publication (Box 1, Folder 9)
      Notes: v.48:no.9 (2007:Feb. 1)
    - Item 3: New York Teacher, 2007; Publication (Box 1, Folder 9)
      Notes: v.48:no.10 (2007:Feb. 15
    - Item 4: New York Teacher, 2007; Publication (Box 1, Folder 9)
      Notes: v.48:no.11 (2007:Mar. 1)
    - Item 5: New York Teacher, 2007; Publication (Box 1, Folder 9)
      Notes: v.48:no.13 (2007:Mar. 29)
    - Item 6: New York Teacher, 2007; Publication (Box 1, Folder 9)
      Notes: v.48:no.15 (2007:Apr. 26)
    - Item 7: New York Teacher, 2007; Publication (Box 1, Folder 9)
      Notes: v.48:no.16 (2007:May 10)
    - Item 8: New York Teacher, 2007; Publication (Box 1, Folder 9)
      Notes: v.48:no.17 (2007:May 24)
    - Item 9: New York Teacher, 2007; Publication (Box 1, Folder 9)
      Notes: v.48:no.18 (2007:June 7)
    - Item 10: New York Teacher, 2007; Publication (Box 1, Folder 9)
      Notes: v.49:no.1 (2007:Sept. 6)
    - Item 11: New York Teacher, 2007; Publication (Box 1, Folder 9)
      Notes: v.49:no.2 (2007:Sept. 20)
    - Item 12: New York Teacher, 2007; Publication (Box 1, Folder 9)
      Notes: v.49:no.4 (2007:Oct. 18)
    - Item 13: New York Teacher, 2007; Publication (Box 1, Folder 9)
      Notes: v.49:no.5 (2007:Nov. 1)
    - Item 14: New York Teacher, 2007; Publication (Box 1, Folder 9)
      Notes: v.49:no.6 (2007:Nov. 15)
  - Box: 1, Folder: 10, Publication (Box 1, Folder 10)
    - Item 1: New York Teacher, 2008; Publication (Box 1, Folder 10)
      Notes: v.49:no.11 (2008:Feb. 28)
    - Item 2: New York Teacher, 2008; Publication (Box 1, Folder 10)
      Notes: v.49:no.12 (2008:Mar. 13)
    - Item 3: New York Teacher, 2008; Publication (Box 1, Folder 10)
      Notes: v.49:no.13 (2008:Mar. 27)
    - Item 4: New York Teacher, 2008; Publication (Box 1, Folder 10)
      Notes: v.49:no.16 (2008:May 8)
    - Item 5: New York Teacher, 2008; Publication (Box 1, Folder 10)
      Notes: v.49:no.18 (2008:June 7)
    - Item 6: New York Teacher, 2008; Publication (Box 1, Folder 10)
      Notes: v.50:no.1 (2008:Sept. 12)
    - Item 7: New York Teacher, 2008; Publication (Box 1, Folder 10)
      Notes: v.50:no.4 (2008:Oct. 23)
    - Item 8: New York Teacher, 2008; Publication (Box 1, Folder 10)
      Notes: v.50:no.5 (2008:Nov. 6)
    - Item 9: New York Teacher, 2008; Publication (Box 1, Folder 10)
      Notes: v.50:no.6 (2008:Nov. 20)
  - Box: 1, Folder: 11, Publication (Box 1, Folder 11)
    - Item 1: New York Teacher, 2009; Publication (Box 1, Folder 11)
      Notes: v.50:no.10 (2009:Feb. 19)
    - Item 2: New York Teacher, 2009; Publication (Box 1, Folder 11)
      Notes: v.50:no.13 (2009:Arp. 2)
    - Item 3: New York Teacher, 2009; Publication (Box 1, Folder 11)
      Notes: v.51:no.3 (2009:Oct. 15)
    - Item 4: New York Teacher, 2009; Publication (Box 1, Folder 11)
      Notes: v.51:no.4 (2009:Oct. 29)
    - Item 5: New York Teacher, 2009; Publication (Box 1, Folder 11)
      Notes: v.51:no.5 (2009:Nov. 12)
    - Item 6: New York Teacher, 2009; Publication (Box 1, Folder 11)
      Notes: v.51:no.6 (2009:Nov. 26)
    - Item 7: New York Teacher, 2009; Publication (Box 1, Folder 11)
      Notes: v.51:no.7 (2009:Dec. 17)
  - Box: 1, Folder: 12, Publication (Box 1, Folder 12)
    - Item 1: New York Teacher, 2010; Publication (Box 1, Folder 12)
      Notes: v.51:no.8 (2010:Jan. 21)
    - Item 2: New York Teacher, 2010; Publication (Box 1, Folder 12)
      Notes: v.51:no.9 (2010:Feb. 4)
    - Item 3: New York Teacher, 2010; Publication (Box 1, Folder 12)
      Notes: v.51:no.10 (2010:Feb. 18)
    - Item 4: New York Teacher, 2010; Publication (Box 1, Folder 12)
      Notes: v.51:no.11 (2010:Mar. 4)
    - Item 5: New York Teacher, 2010; Publication (Box 1, Folder 12)
      Notes: v.51:no.12 (2010:Mar. 18)
    - Item 6: New York Teacher, 2010; Publication (Box 1, Folder 12)
      Notes: v.51:no.14 (2010:Arp. 15)
    - Item 7: New York Teacher, 2010; Publication (Box 1, Folder 12)
      Notes: v.51:no.15 (2010:May 6)
    - Item 8: New York Teacher, 2010; Publication (Box 1, Folder 12)
      Notes: v.51:no.16 (2010:May 20)
    - Item 9: New York Teacher, 2010; Publication (Box 1, Folder 12)
      Notes: v.51:no.17 (2010:June 3)
    - Item 10: New York Teacher, 2010; Publication (Box 1, Folder 12)
      Notes: v.51:no.18 (2010:June 17)
    - Item 11: New York Teacher, 2010; Publication (Box 1, Folder 12)
      Notes: v.51:no.13 (2010:Apr. 1)
- Box: 2, Folder: 1, Publication (Box 2, Folder 1)
  - Item 1: Health & Safety, 2010; Publication (Box 2, Folder 1)
    Notes: v.16:no.1 (2010:Winter)
  - Item 2: Health & Safety, 2005; Publication (Box 2, Folder 1)
    Notes: v.12:no.2 (2005:Fall)
  - Item 3: Health & Safety, 2006; Publication (Box 2, Folder 1)
    Notes: v.12:no.3 (2006:Winter)
  - Item 4: Health & Safety, 2006; Publication (Box 2, Folder 1)
    Notes: v.12:no.4 (2006:Spring)
  - Item 5: Health & Safety, 2006; Publication (Box 2, Folder 1)
    Notes: v.13:no.1 (2006:Fall)
  - Item 6: Health & Safety, 2007; Publication (Box 2, Folder 1)
    Notes: v.13:no.2 (2007:Winter)
  - Item 7: Health & Safety, 2007; Publication (Box 2, Folder 1)
    Notes: v.13:no.3 (2007:Spring)
  - Item 8: Health & Safety, 2007; Publication (Box 2, Folder 1)
    Notes: v.14:no.1 (2007:Fall)
  - Item 9: Health & Safety, 2007; Publication (Box 2, Folder 1)
    Notes: v.14:no.1 (2007:Fall). Copy 2.
  - Item 10: Health & Safety, 2008; Publication (Box 2, Folder 1)
    Notes: v.14:no.2 (2008:Winter)
  - Item 11: Health & Safety, 2008; Publication (Box 2, Folder 1)
    Notes: v.14:no.2 (2008:Winter). Copy 2.
  - Item 12: Health & Safety, 2008; Publication (Box 2, Folder 1)
    Notes: v.14:no.3 (2008:Spring)
  - Item 13: Health & Safety, 2008; Publication (Box 2, Folder 1)
    Notes: v.14:no.3 (2008:Spring). Copy 2.
  - Item 14: Health & Safety, 2008; Publication (Box 2, Folder 1)
    Notes: v.15:no.1 (2008:Fall)
  - Item 15: Health & Safety, 2008; Publication (Box 2, Folder 1)
    Notes: v.15:no.1 (2008:Fall). Copy 2.
  - Item 16: Health & Safety, 2009; Publication (Box 2, Folder 1)
    Notes: v.15:no.2 (2009:Winter)
  - Item 17: Health & Safety, 2009; Publication (Box 2, Folder 1)
    Notes: v.15:no.3 (2009:Spring)
  - Item 18: Health & Safety, 2009; Publication (Box 2, Folder 1)
    Notes: v.15:no.4 (2009:Summer)
  - Item 19: Health & Safety, 2010; Publication (Box 2, Folder 1)
    Notes: v.16:no.2 (2010:Spring)
- Box: 2, Folder: 2, Publication (Box 2, Folder 2)
  - Item 1: The Insider, 2005; Publication (Box 2, Folder 2)
    Notes: v.1:no.1 (2005:Fall)
  - Item 2: The Insider, 2005; Publication (Box 2, Folder 2)
    Notes: v.1:no.2 (2005:Winter)
  - Item 3: The Insider, 2006; Publication (Box 2, Folder 2)
    Notes: v.1:no.3 (2006:Spring)
  - Item 4: The Insider, 2006; Publication (Box 2, Folder 2)
    Notes: v.2:no.1 (2006:Fall)
  - Item 5: The Insider, 2007; Publication (Box 2, Folder 2)
    Notes: v.2:no.2 (2007:Winter)
- Box: 2, Folder: 3, Publication (Box 2, Folder 3)
  - Item 1: NYSUT Leader, 2007; Publication (Box 2, Folder 3)
    Notes: v.25:no.19 (2007:May 21)
  - Item 2: NYSUT Leader, 2007; Publication (Box 2, Folder 3)
    Notes: v.25:no.20 (2007:June 8)
  - Item 3: NYSUT Leader, 2007; Publication (Box 2, Folder 3)
    Notes: v.25:no.21 (2007:June 30)
  - Item 4: NYSUT Leader, 2007; Publication (Box 2, Folder 3)
    Notes: v.26:no. 1 (2007:Aug. 24)